hyperli.com 2019-05-15

# Hyperli | Privacy Policy

## **Hyperli Privacy Statement**

Please note that this privacy statement only applies to you if you purchase a product from Hyperli.

This Privacy Statement explains how Hyperli processes and uses information about you. This Privacy Statement applies only to information we process in order to facilitate your purchase of products sold by us on the Hyperli South Africa website, featured on www.hyperli.com). The Site is owned and operated by Hyperli, a South African company, trading from 1st Floor, The Bureaux, 10 North Wharf, Aria Building, 42 Hans Strijdom Ave Ln, Cape Town City Centre, Cape Town, 8000.

This Privacy Statement was adopted as of the Effective Date above, and may be amended from time to time. In the event of a material change, we may notify you of such changes.

### **1.  Personal data collected**

Hyperli is the data owner in respect of your personal data that is necessary to provide you with the products you purchased from us on the Site. This includes information such as your name and delivery address. Hyperli directly processes your data in accordance with the international practices it employs across its business relating to the protection and processing of personal information.

Please note that Hyperli is the data owner in respect of all information you provide or is made available about you when you interact with the Site. This includes, for example, information necessary to create a Hyperli account or to subscribe to email marketing. Your customer relationship is with Hyperli, which processes your personal in accordance with Applicable Privacy Practices and its Privacy Statement.

### **2.  When and Why Hyperli Discloses Information**

We are not in the business of selling or renting personal data. When we process your personal data for the purposes set out in section 2 above, we may pass or share your personal data with third parties, as may be necessary from time to time:

 ***** With affiliated and unaffiliated technical and organisational service providers relevant to our business.  
 ***** To third parties to report or collect on debts owed to us or our suppliers or other business partners.  
 ***** To third parties in order for us to perform contractual obligations toward you, combat fraud or criminal activity, or as part of legal proceedings affecting us.  
 ***** To law enforcement officers or other government officials, to comply with legal orders and government requests, or as needed to support auditing, compliance, and corporate governance functions.

Please note that it is likely some recipients of your data may be located outside of South Africa, in countries with an inadequate level of data protection. You recognise and understand that when you purchase a product, we may pass your personal information to a service provider or business partner who supports delivery of your product to you and that this service provider or business partner may be located (or process your personal data) outside of South Africa.

### **3.  Security of Personal Data**

We process data mainly in electronic form in line with the Applicable Privacy Practices security requirements; Hyperli has implemented an information security program that contains administrative, technical and physical controls that are designed to reasonably safeguard your personal data, including industry-standard encryption technology.  

### **4.  Retention of Personal Data and Your Rights in relation to Personal Data**

We will retain your personal data for as long as necessary to perform our contractual obligations to you and as required by applicable law. Should you wish to know more about the personal data we have about you, you can exercise your rights of access at any time. Should you wish to do so, please email us at support@hyperli.com. You may also write to us at: Hyperli, 1st Floor, The Bureaux, 10 North Wharf, Aria Building, 42 Hans Strijdom Ave Ln, Cape Town City Centre, Cape Town, 8000.

Please note that while we are ready to assist you, we cannot always delete records of past interactions and transactions. For example, we are required to retain records relating to previous purchases for financial reporting and compliance reasons.
